Guide to the League of Women Voters of the Fairfax Area records, 1948-2009
George Mason University Libraries
- Series 6: Subject Files, 1953-2006; 29 boxes
  - Voters Service Unit Workshop, 1973 - 1987 (Box 62, Folder 10)
  - "What's on the Ballot" plus Debates, 1981-1991 (Box 62, Folder 11)
  - Women's History Month, 1995 - 2003 (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - Women's Suffrage, 1995 (Box 63, Folder 2)
  - Zoning Amendment, 1989 (Box 63, Folder 3)
  - Zoning, 1992 - 1994 (Box 63, Folder 4)
- Series 7: Oral History, 1995-1996; (2 boxes)
  Series 7 contains records relating to the oral history collected about the LWVFA. The series is in 2 boxes and contains files and audio tapes.
  - Martha Pennino, 1995-1996 (Box 63, Folder 5)
  - LWVFA Notable Women Oral History Project: Nancy Brown, 1995-1996 (Box 63, Folder 6)
  - LWVFA Notable Women Oral History Project: Inta Sraders, 1995-1996 (Box 63, Folder 7)
  - LWVFA Notable Women Oral History Project: Audrey Moore, 1995-1996 (Box 63, Folder 8)
  - LWVFA Notable Women Oral History Project: Kathryn Brooks, 1995-1996 (Box 63, Folder 9)
  - LWVFA Notable Women Oral History Project: Ann Kahn, 1995-1996 (Box 63, Folder 10)
  - LWVFA Notable Women Oral History Project: Muriel Ferris, 1995 (Box 63, Folder 11)
  - LWVFA Notable Women Oral History Project: Flora Crater, 1995-1996 (Box 65, Folder 1)
  - LWVFA Notable Women Oral History Project: Jean Packard, 1995-1996 (Box 65, Folder 2)
  - Oral History Tapes, 1995 - 1996 (Box 64)
    Contains 9 audiotape cassettes with the oral histories of Martha Pennino, Nancy Brown, Inta Sraders, Audrey Morre, Kathryn Brooks, Ann Kahn, Muriel Ferris, Flora Crater, and Jean Packard.
- Series 8: Photographs, 2002; (0.25 box)
  Series 8 contains photographs of the LWVFA at various events and activities. The series is arranged in one box.
  - Photos, Undated (Box 65, Folder 3)
- Series 9: Electronic Records, 1994; (0.25 box)
  Series 9 contains electronic records in ASCII format on 3.5 inch and 5.25 inch floppy discs. The records accompany the 1994 Election voters guides and candidate questionaires.
  - Electronic Records, 1994 (Box 65, Folder 4)
- Series 10: Oversize, 1964-1980s; (5 boxes)
  Series 10 contains the oversized materials and memorabilia of the LWVFA. The series is arranged in 5 boxes.
  - LWVFA Betacam Tape, 1981 (Box 66)
    Contains 2 Betacam tapes dealing with Construction Site Safety
  - Buttons and Memorabilia, Undated (Box 67)
    This box contains 16 buttons, a bumper sticker, a keychain, a napkin and 3 bags of nametags from various League programs and activities.
  - Scrapbook, 1964 - 1965 (Box 68)
  - Scrapbook and Memorabilia, 1981 (Box 69)
    Contains a scrapbook, a LWVFA sign, and a pennant
  - Apron, 1980s (Box 70)